http://www.drpower.com/pages/content/company/privacy

get exclusive savings
right in your inbox!
Get the inside scoop! Sign up for
DR's email mailing list for exclusive savings, weekly specials,
current promotions, new product news and more.
Success! You've been added to the
mailing list.
Privacy Policy
Thank you for visiting www.drpower.com. When you visit our website, your security and privacy becomes our responsibility. That's why every transaction you make with us is treated with safety, security, and confidentiality.
Important notice for California residents!
Secure Shopping
We realize that you may have concerns about placing an order online and sending us your credit card number over the Internet. For your security, orders placed on our site are encrypted using TLS technology, which ensures that your transaction is protected. The information you send to us via the Internet can be trusted to arrive privately and unaltered. Please note that e-mail is not encrypted and is not considered a secure means of transmitting credit card numbers. If you would like to learn more about Secure Shopping on our website, see below. Or, if you have any questions regarding Secure Shopping on our website, please contact us via Live Chat, email or phone.
Your Credit Card Number is Secure
When you use your credit card to shop our Site, rest assured that the transaction is secure. Our servers use (TLS), an advanced encryption technology that works with Google Chrome (version 40 and above), Microsoft Internet Explorer (version 11.0 and above), Microsoft Edge, Firefox (version 35 and above), Safari (version 8.0 and above). Note: You should always update your browsers to the latest versions to mitigate vulnerabilities. This technology safeguards your personal information and guarantees privacy.
How to Check the Security of Your Browser
To check the security of your connection, look at the lower left- or right-hand corner of your browser window after accessing the server. If you see an unbroken key or a closed lock (depending on your browser), then TLS is active and the page you are accessing is being transmitted by TLS. You can also double-check by looking at the URL line of your browser. When accessing a secure page, the first characters of the site address will change from "http" to "https."
Some versions of browsers and some firewalls don't permit communication through secure servers. In that case, you won't be able to connect to the server and, therefore, won't be able to place an order through an insecure connection. If you cannot access the secure server for any reason, please call us TOLL-FREE at 1-800-687-6575 to place your order.
If you still feel more comfortable ordering over the phone, please call us TOLL-FREE at 1-800-687-6575. One of our Customer Support Representatives will be happy to help you.
Your Privacy Online
The DR® Power Equipment website is here as a service to our customers, and we're committed to making it private. As a rule, we do not collect any personal information about you when you visit our website, unless you provide it to us. If you place an online order or request a catalog, we do ask for information such as your name, mailing address, telephone number, and e-mail address. If you do give us your postal or e-mail address, you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on sales events or new products. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please contact us.
Occasionally, we may share your name and mailing address with companies we believe may be of interest to you. If you prefer not to receive mailings from other companies, please contact us.
To help us understand how people use our website and how we might improve it, we do track, in aggregate, how visitors access and use our site. So that we can better understand the strength of our marketing efforts, we also make a record of when people click through to our website from an advertisement, search engine listing, and other sites where we pay for representation.
If you would like to learn more about Your Privacy Online, please see below. Or, if you have any questions regarding Your Privacy Online, please contact us.
Information We Collect Online and How it is Used
We gather information about visitors to our site for two reasons: to provide a product or service you have requested and to improve our website, so that we may better serve your needs. The only information we collect about you, personally, is the information you choose to provide. In several areas of our site, we ask you to provide information by filling out and submitting an online form. These areas include:
Catalog Requests: To send you one of our catalogs, we need your name and address. At this point, we may also ask a few questions, such as, "How did you hear about us?" Answering these questions is optional and we do not share the answers to these questions with anyone.
E-mail Mailing List: For subscriptions to our e-mail program, we need only your e-mail address. We do not sell, rent, or trade your e-mail address with anyone, for any reason.
Purchases: In order to process and deliver your purchases, we need your name, address, phone number, e-mail address, and credit card information.
In addition to the above, each time you visit our website we do collect information about how you accessed our site and the particular pages you viewed. The reason we gather this type of information is to better understand what customers want when they visit www.drpower.com. However, it's important to note that we do not analyze this information on an individual visitor level. Instead, we analyze the combined data from the thousands of visitors to our website. As we study the data we find that trends often appear that can help us improve our website. For instance, with this data we can learn which parts of our website are accessed most frequently, or which search engines visitors use to find our website.
Additionally, we have carefully selected affiliates to apply third-party advertising technology to serve ads when you visit our site and sites where we advertise. This advertising technology uses information about your visits to our site and the sites where we advertise (excluding your name, address or other personal information) to serve our ads to you. In the course of serving our advertisements to you, a unique cookie may be placed or recognized on your browser. In addition, these affiliates use "web beacons", which are small strings of code delivered by a transparent graphic image on a web page for purposes of transferring data, to help manage our online advertising. These web beacons enable our ad server to recognize a browser's cookie when a browser visits this site and to learn which banner ads bring users to our site. We have implemented the following Google Analytics Advertising Features: Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting and Google Analytics Remarketing.
These features allow us to advertise based on demographic and interest data as gathered and determined by Google. To opt out of Google Advertising features please visit this link https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/. The information we collect and share through this technology is not personally identifiable.
Any information we collect about our customers is stored in a secure database.
We may from time to time contract with third party vendors to serve ads to our customers on our behalf across the internet or to send our catalogs to customers whom we think may be interested in our products or services. To do this, the vendors will collect anonymous information about your visits to our Web site and your interaction with our products and services. This anonymous information is collected through the use of a cookie or pixel tag — industry standard technology used by most major Web sites. No personally identifiable information is collected in this process. They may also pool the anonymous information that they collect with other sources of information not collected during your visit to our website, which may include your name and mailing address, for purposes of determining whether you might be interested in receiving marketing literature.
If you do not wish for cookies or pixel tags to be placed on your computer, most commercially available web browsers permit you to prevent that from taking place. To opt-out of receiving our marketing materials, you may email us at customerservice@drpower.com or call us at 1-800-687-6575.
Information We Do Not Collect
When you visit our site, we do not collect your name, e-mail address or any other personal information unless you provide it to us, as described above.
About Cookies and How We Use Them
A cookie is a small file that a Website puts on your computer's hard drive so that it can remember you at a later time. This file contains nothing more than a 32-digit code. It does not contain your name, address, or any other personal information. Our cookies do not identify an individual user specifically, such as by name or address.
We use cookies for two reasons. (1) Cookies allow us to retain any items you've placed in your shopping basket, should you decide to leave your shopping basket and view other areas on our site, or other websites. If you do this, when you are done and return to your shopping basket, the items you selected are still there for you to buy. (2) Cookies also tell us whether you have visited drpower.com previously, and help us determine whether you came to our website from a particular Internet link or banner advertisement.It's important to note that the data we gather via cookies is analyzed in aggregate. This means we analyze the trends established by thousands of visitors through our site. We do not analyze data on the individual customer level.
How We Use E-mail
We use e-mail for two purposes: To notify you about the status of an order you placed on our website and to provide information you have requested.
After you place an order on our site, you will receive an e-mail message confirming your order. You will receive this only if you have provided your e-mail address during checkout or when registering. If you signed up to receive our DR® Savings or Weekly Special E-mail, we'll occasionally send you messages about new products, special promotions, or online sales. Any time we contact you by e-mail, you will be given the choice to opt out of receiving further e-mails from us. If you currently receive our e-mails and do not wish to continue receiving them, please opt out here.
Information We Do Not Share With Others
Country Home Products does not share, sell or trade e-mail addresses, telephone numbers, information collected as part of a survey or specific details about you or your household, except as described above in "Your Privacy Online".
In the event that we merge with, are acquired by, or sell a substantial portion of our business to another company, or if we engage in a similar corporate transaction, we reserve the right to transfer the information we have collected from visitors to our website and from our customers to the successor company. This successor's use of this information would be governed by our privacy policy in effect at that time, as may be revised by the successor after the date of any such transaction.
We may change or modify this Privacy Policy from time to time. These changes may affect what information we collect and how we use it. If we modify this Privacy Policy, we will post the revised Privacy Policy on this Web Site. You should check this Web Site regularly to see if any recent changes to this Privacy Policy have occurred.
Your use of this website represents your consent to our collection and use of your information as explained in this privacy policy. In addition, your use of this website represents your agreement to the Terms of Use represented in this policy.
Visit Our Legal Page
California Residents
Your Rights Under the California Consumer Privacy Act
The California Consumer Privacy Act states residents of the state of California have the right to:
Request the personal information collected about them
Request the personal information collected about them be deleted
Opt out of the sale or sharing of your personal information
The categories and types of information collected are listed in detail above in our privacy policy.
Making a request
In order to request disclosure, deletion, or opt-out of sale or sharing personal information, please contact us using the form on the contact us page, or call our contact center at 1-800-687-6575.
Indicate the nature of the request, and provide your full name, mailing address, email address and phone number for verification purposes.
If making a request on behalf of another individual, please use the same method as indicated in the previous bullet.
We will contact you and for additional information.
Please be able to provide proof that you are authorized to act on another’s behalf.
Non-Discrimination
We will in no way discriminate against California residents who choose to exercise their privacy rights.
This privacy policy was last updated January 1, 2020.
